export default {
  easy: [
    {
      id: "1",
      question: "Who created nigeria flag",
      choices: ["Taiwo Akinwunmi", "Bayo sunday"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      question: "How old is nigeria",
      choices: ["61", "62", "67", "none of the above"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      id: "3",
      question: "Nigeria gain her independence in year",
      choices: ["1961", "1963", "1960", "1964"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      id: "4",
      question: "Who colonize nigeria",
      choices: [
        "Elizabeth the frist",
        "Elizabeth the second",
        "Elizabeth the third",
        "Elizabeth the fourth"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      id: "5",
      question: "The third flag color of nigeria flag reperesent what",
      choices: ["peace", "propsperity", "comfort", "agriculture"],
      answer: 3
    }
  ],
  normal: [
    {
      id: "6",
      question: "Who created nigeria flag6",
      choices: ["Taiwo Akinwunmi", "Bayo sunday"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      question: "How old is nigeria7",
      choices: ["61", "62", "67", "none of the above"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      question: "Nigeria gain her independence in year8",
      choices: ["1961", "1963", "1960", "1964"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      id: "9",
      question: "Who colonize nigeria9",
      choices: [
        "Elizabeth the frist",
        "Elizabeth the second",
        "Elizabeth the third",
        "Elizabeth the fourth"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      question: "The third flag color of nigeria flag reperesent what10",
      choices: ["peace", "propsperity", "comfort", "agriculture"],
      answer: 3
    }
  ],
  hard: [
    {
      id: "11",
      question: "Who created nigeria flag11",
      choices: ["Taiwo Akinwunmi", "Bayo sunday"],
      answer: 0
    },
    {
      id: "12",
      question: "How old is nigeria12",
      choices: ["61", "62", "67", "none of the above"],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      id: "13",
      question: "Nigeria gain her independence in year13",
      choices: ["1961", "1963", "1960", "1964"],
      answer: 2
    },
    {
      id: "14",
      question: "Who colonize nigeria14",
      choices: [
        "Elizabeth the frist",
        "Elizabeth the second",
        "Elizabeth the third",
        "Elizabeth the fourth"
      ],
      answer: 1
    },
    {
      id: "15",
      question: "The third flag color of nigeria flag reperesent what15",
      choices: ["peace", "propsperity", "comfort", "agriculture"],
      answer: 3
    }
  ]
};
